123teachme.com 2010-11-19

# 123TeachMe - Privacy Policy

Last modified: March 17, 2010

At 123TeachMe we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites provided by 123TeachMe or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. 

123TeachMe adheres to the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement. Please visit the site below for more information.  

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website. We welcome your comments!

**Information we collect and how we use it**

We offer a number of services that do NOT require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:  
Cookies – When you visit 123TeachMe, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends. 123TeachMe also uses cookies to help advertisers serve and manage ads.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Log information**  – When you access 123TeachMe services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

**User communications**  – When you send email or other communications to 123TeachMe, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.  
Gadgets – The information collected by 123TeachMe when you enable a gadget or other application is processed under this Privacy Policy.

**Links** – 123TeachMe may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our website and provide the user with information or services they desire.

**Other sites**  – This Privacy Policy applies to 123TeachMe only. We do not exercise control over the sites that may advertise or place links on 123Teachme. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Please exersize caution before providing them with any information.

123TeachMe only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

Providing our services, including the display of customized content and advertising;  
Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;  
Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;  
Protecting the rights or property of 123TeachMe or our users; and  
Developing new services.

123TeachMe processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

**Choices for personal information**

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some 123TeachMe features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

123TeachMe uses the DoubleClick advertising cookie to help advertisers serve and manage ads. You can view, edit, and manage your ads preferences associated with this cookie by accessing the Ads Preferences Manager. In addition, you may choose to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie at any time by using DoubleClick’s opt-out cookie.  
Information sharing

123TeachMe only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of 123TeachMe in the following limited circumstances:

We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.  
We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of 123TeachMe, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If 123TeachMe becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.

Please contact us for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to 123TeachMe employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Data integrity**

123TeachMe processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Enforcement**

123TeachMe regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or 123TeachMe’s treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
